[{"answer": "So the president looks mean there.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "How are you tonight?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "I don't -- there's no legislation regarding -- with regards to abortion that I'm familiar with that -- that would become part of my agenda.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Do you intend to pursue any legislation specifically regarding abortion?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "He's referring -- listen.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "So which is it?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "I think -- no.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Do you see it as an evolution or do you see it -- see it as a rather cynical exercise?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, Piers, you know, President Obama knew Ambassador Chris Stevens.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Should heads roll?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Piers, I -- I can't even believe that you would suggest that Ambassador Rice would make deliberately misleading statements.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "That it had been planned?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Well, I think as more information came out, the initial information that would -- that they had was perceived to be that the attack was the result of protests and as the investigation has worn on, which is the responsible way to deal with it, we've come out and the administration has said, well, it's clear that now it was the result of a terrorist attack.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "-- that Ambassador Rice was simply wrong?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Piers, Piers, because these investigations are complicated and detailed and rather than say absolutely nothing, rather than -- you know, than not give information to the American people, Ambassador Rice went out and talked about what they believed to be happening at the time with the information on -- from the intelligence community that she had.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "And secondly, what -- why, with the world's intelligence, amass that you have at the White House and the Pentagon and so on, why could you make statements four, five days after (INAUDIBLE) with completely the wrong explanation for what has provoked this attack?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Piers, it is not, it is not OK for you to be saying that the administration was putting out completely false statements.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Pretty un-American to be putting out completely false statements before you know the facts, isn't it?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "It doesn't mean that it wasn't deliberate.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "No, I --", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Who could have thought that we'd be in this position?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "No, I think both of us secretly thought Barack Obama was cruising to victory.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Is that what you thought?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "It's funny I was also watching that, I'm thinking, nobody was having more fun during this election than Bill Clinton, you know?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "It could hurt him and when I was watching that clip, in fact, I was thinking about animation in Clinton's -- you know, voice and face, and I was thinking about Barack Obama during the last debate where he just look like he didn't want to be there.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Could it in a funny way hurt him?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "There is nothing wrong with that position.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "I mean what is wrong with that position?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "I think because the expectation is heavy that Ryan wins by a lot, I think Biden wins.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Biden versus Ryan, who's going to win?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Again, because of expectations, I think we're going to be talking about how good Obama was because no one -- everyone is going to be comparing it to his last debate.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "And Romney-Obama next week?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "I mean Governor Romney has made very clear that if a bill comes to his desk, that overturns \"Roe versus Wade\" that he will be fully supportive of that.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "So is this a lie?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "It's not that his position changed, it's that he says that, you know, he -- there is a difference between if a bill came to my desk, I'd sign it and I'm going to go to Congress and fight for a bill.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Which one is he?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "No, I think it's an important issue, but I think fixing the economy is the most important thing.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "You don't really care about abortion as an issue?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "I'm not going to speculate on what happened in the White House.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What the hell were you doing, Barack?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "I don't think Paul Ryan is on the menu.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Or is everyone really waiting for the next one?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "It is bipartisan, transatlantic and private.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "What is it about?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Well, we focus on areas where we think the business community can really be involved.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "How do we get the elevator working again?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Well, I think that, yes, we need to do that.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Should more business leaders be doing this?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "I really think we have laid the question down to ourselves of we're asking what the business community needs to do.", "docId": "121010pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Which of the two leaders right now, pound for pound, dollar for dollar, would you say gives the best chance of fulfilling what you would like to see?", "qSentId": 588}]